css4me.com 2013-05-19

# Privacy Policy : CSS4Me

###### Privacy Policy

We understands the importance of keeping your personal and other information private and secure(including but not limited to text, images, designs, layouts).

We have adopted strict policies and guidelines of security and confidentiality. On our website, we use the latest website security measures. In addition, only employees trained in the proper handling of customer information are able to view your information.

We have created this privacy in order to demonstrate just how committed we are to protecting the privacy of our Clients and the privacy of other visitors to our web sites. This statement explains why we ask for the information that we do, how we will use it, and what access you have to the information we collect.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

We collect and store personal information from you through order submission, surveys, the use of enquiry and other forms and each time you e-mail us your details.

We collects and stores the following information of the order placed: name, telephone number, address, e-mail address and citizenship. We also collect and store the following personal information when you sign up to receive our E-mail Newsletter: name, address, and electronic mail address. All of this information is stored internally.

Your information will only be used by us. Your email will be used by us to send you regular email with details of order and offers. We will also use your information to ensure that you are supplied with the most appropriate content.

By accepting this policy, you authorize us to contact you by email, telephone, mobile SMS and direct mail.

Use of Cookies: A cookie is a very small text file that is placed on your hard drive by a Web server. Cookies cannot be executed like programs or used as viruses, and the server that placed them can only read them. A cookie cannot access your hard drive and obtain personal information about you, unless you have supplied your information to the site delivering the cookie; it can only be used to store information that you have given the site (by filling out an online order form, for example)

We uses cookies to build up a profile of our regular clients, to tell our server whether or not you have visited us before. We use this information to provide you with improved service. Cookies can enhance your online experience. Most Web browsers allow you to customize your cookies settings.

All personal, cookie and session ID information are made available to our employees to enable us and any related third parties to deal more effectively with any enquiry you make.

If we are going to use your personally information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via e-mail. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. However, if you have opted out of all communication with us, then you will not be contacted, nor will your personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post the notice on our web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post the notice we will also e-mail users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.
